So here's some things that people are talking about that I don't care about.
The demolishing of the White House.
Oh, that element of the White House is where all the women existed in the White House, etc.
I don't care.
Then you aren't understanding the symbolism of the demolishing.
If it took them demolishing a wing of the White House for you to understand the trajectory of terror that this administration has against women,
then you are very, very, very far behind.
I don't know if you remember, but the reproductive rights of Roe v. Wade were actually, yeah, rolled back.
And you know who didn't handle that?
You know who didn't make that a preventative proposition?
You know who actually didn't prevent that?
Right.
Joe Biden.
Yeah.
He could have codified Roe v. Wade.
Didn't do it.
And he did.
You know who else could have done it?
Bay Rock.
Didn't.
I don't know why you all seem to think that the performative spaces of the White House where first wives, who, by the way, are imperialist enablers, got to hang out and have events and, I don't know, flower arrange, is something that needed to be protected, is beyond me.
Y'all love a good symbolism, baby.
I respect it as a writer.
But as a realist, I couldn't give two hot dams about demolishing the White House.
Take it all down.
It's slaves that built it anyway.
White women, I want you to know something.
When black women see white-on-white violence in a corporate space, it is hilarious to us.
So I just want you to know that the next time that you find yourself about to argue with another white woman, look around.
You might be bringing joy to someone's day.
Head to AmandaSeals.com to get your tickets to the live stream performance and book release of my latest work, What Would the Ancestors Say?